Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Ben & Jerry's most popular
flavor, Halfbaked. Let me show you how
to make it. So, halfbaked technically
has vanilla and chocolate ice cream, but
you can't really do that in the Ninja
Creamy. So, you kind of just have to
choose one. I chose chocolate. I'll put
the vanilla based recipe in the caption
below as well. So, feel free to pick
either one. It's going to come out
amazing either way. But what matters
even more than the base are the mixins.
We all know that Halfbake is packed with
brownies and cookie dough. And we need
to recreate that, but in a healthier
way. So, the best substitutions I've
found are the Alpha Prime Bites protein
brownies. Just chop those up and throw
them on top along with the Fuel Protein
Cookie Dough Bites. The combination of
these two add almost 15 grams of protein
and make it taste like real Ben &
Jerry's halfbaked.